unitedliberty.org 2011-05-29

# Privacy Policy | United Liberty | Free Market - Individual Liberty - Limited Government

Thank you for visiting United Liberty.  We understand your privacy is of upmost importance, and we want to assure you that we take it as seriously as you do.  The following describes our standard policies and the steps we take to protect our users’ privacy.

### Updates

The internet changes rapidly and United Liberty will make all efforts to keep up with any developments that affect the privacy of the personal information you entrust to us.  When changes are necessary, we will update our Privacy Policy, available for viewing at www.unitedliberty.org/privacy-policy.   If you are a registered user, we may also send you an email noting the alterations.

### What Information Do We Collect?

You do not have to be a registered user to visit and enjoy United Liberty, however there are certain privileges afforded to those who choose to do so.  Upon registering, we require the following basic login information: email address, username and password.  Registered users also have the opportunity to personalize their Profile Page by adding their full name, homepage, short bio, gender, age, location, social networking site usernames (such as Twitter, Facebook, etc.), an avatar, and custom signature.  Becoming a registered user will also allow you to submit content ideas, participate on the United Liberty message board, and view our Site ad-free.  The information added to a user’s Profile Page will be publicly available.

Some information may also be collected by the use of cookies.  These cookies allow us to provide a more enriched user experience while never allowing us to personally identify users.

### Information We Don’t Collect

The staff at United Liberty strives to keep our content “family-friendly” but we have no interest in collecting information from children under the age of 13. United Liberty does not target our content to children nor do we knowingly collect personal information from users under the age of 13.

### What Do We Do With Your Information?

United Liberty, from time to time, may send an update about the website, or other particularly newsworthy events. We may also occasionally send a message from one of our affiliate partners. At no time does any third-party group have access to your information.  Users will always have the option to opt-out of our e-mail list.

United Liberty keeps track of the number of people that visit our Site and the individual pages.  The cookies allow us to also keep track of the browser types and IP addresses of our visitors, but this data is collected in aggregate form only.  It will not be used to identify your personal information.

At times, United Liberty may contract with other companies in order to provide certain services to our users or improve our Site.  If your information needs to be made available to one of these companies in order to utilize their services, they will be required to sign a confidentiality agreement that will provide equal protection for your information, as compared to our own Privacy Policy.

### What We Don’t Do With Your Information

It is United Liberty’s policy to never sell your personal information to another entity.  However, your information will be made available to government or law enforcement agencies if we believe we are compelled to do so by law.  If United Liberty is ever sold or merges with another company, your information will be passed on to the new administrators as part of our assets.

### How Do We Secure Your Information?

We take all efforts to make sure that your information is never stolen, lost, altered or allowed to be accessed without the proper authorization.  Several methods are used to this end, including encryption and password protection.

### How Do You Change Your Information?

At any time, you will be able to change or delete the information in your Profile Page.  If you have posted other information as a comment on an article or in the message board and you would like it removed, contact the administrators at United Liberty and we’d be happy to do that for you.  Simply send an email detailing the changes that need to be made to [info@unitedliberty.org](mailto:info@unitedliberty.org).

### Outbound Links

Throughout United Liberty, you will find many links to 3rd party websites.  Linking to these sites doesn’t constitute an endorsement or necessarily mean the staff at United Liberty agrees with the opinions expressed at these sites.  Please visit them at your own risk.

Thank you again for visiting United Liberty and we hope that you will come to our Site frequently.  If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, feel free to send us an email at [info@unitedliberty.org](mailto:info@unitedliberty.org).

United Liberty reserves the right to change or alter this Privacy Policy at any time.

This Privacy Policy was last updated: Jan 6, 2009  
This Privacy Policy is effective as of: Jan 6, 2009
